

Addy Hebou

Front End Engineer

Contact

(240) 595-9273

× addyhebou@gmail.com

36 St. Marks Pl, New York, NY

in linkedin.com/in/addyhebou

addyhebou.github.io/CS-Portfolio-Site

Awards

Eagle Scout Recipient

Education

Aug 2018 - May 2022

New York University

B.S Computer Science

Core Courses:

- Dynamic Web Applications
- UX/UI Design Applications
- Data Structures & Algorithms
- Object-Oriented Programming
- Operating Systems

Aug 2014 - May 2018

North Point High School

Diploma

Software

Video

Adobe Premiere Pro



Design

Figma Invision

Adobe Illustrator



Audio Production

Logic Pro X ***

About

Addy is a student passionate about developing web apps in entertainment-related industries, especially the music industry. He has a variety of knowledge spanning from React & JavaScript experience to UX/UI design applications to his web development process.

Work Experience

Matty Beats Management

Feb 2021 - New York, NY • Junior Front-End Engineer

Developed structure & designs of web apps, web design, and program dynamic web applications to to market music production management company

Music Tech Startup

Aug 2020 - Oct 2020 New York, NY • Junior Software Engineer

Researched, designed, and wrote object-oriented programs to maximize music artists' listening rates and playlists by writing through Python

Girl Scouts of Greater New York

Nov 2019 - Feb 2020 New York, NY • Web Development Instructor

Developed and taught Girl Scouts HTML5 and CSS to develop websites to serve as their Girl Scout Gold Award final project

Skills

Language

- HTML5 (2 years)
- CSS & SASS (2 years)
- JavaScript (2 years)
- Python (3 years)

Framework

· React (1.5 year)

Libraries/API

- React (1.5 year)
- Node.js (1.5 year)

Tools

- Visual Studio Code
- · Git, Github, Bitbucket